[{"answer": "We are expecting for him to sign that tonight.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "When can we expect to see President Obama actually signing all this off?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Mr. President, do you believe this is going to happen all be over again in a few months?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Is there any doubt really that there has been a big win for the White House tonight and a big defeat for the Republicans?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "-- Well, particularly inside the Republican leadership, not just in the Senate, but the House.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Look, here is the thing.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "Is he conceivable that he could emerge despite your misgivings just now as a potential nominee for Republicans, and could they win an election with somebody like him at the helm?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "If it is at the White House, it probably wouldn't sit there very long before he signs it.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "How long could we expect it to sit there before President Obama signs it?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "We have got a lot of work we need to do together, and we have to work across the aisle to get it done.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Is this all bipartisan joy tonight?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I do believe it was a worthy objective, Obama Care has significant issues and problems.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Did the Republicans really, do you think feel that they have suffered a massive defeat here or is it a temporary setback?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "I voted with it.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "And, congressman, which way did you vote tonight?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "I presume that you voted in favor of it, as well, right?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "I think a lot of that stuff ends up being kind of gimmicky.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Is it time, Josh Barro, that we considered actually bringing in some kind of severely punitive measure like that which focused all the politicians' minds in Washington?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "If you have grown-ups who will sit down and take a look at blue ribbon panel after blue ribbon panel of debt commission recommendations and everybody has to give something up and make hard choices and may be from that get re-elected, then you could solve the problem with the $17 trillion debt and deficits, and you can move forward.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Is it possible to avoid all of this when you have a $17 trillion national debt?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "IZZA: Well, this is a giant waste of time and makes you want to, you know, leave Washington and not cover politics anymore.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "What are you feeling?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Hold on.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Come on Ben Ferguson, what do you make of this?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "I am assuming.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Can we get confirmation on that?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "I think he is a brilliant guy that is going to end up being a hero absolutely coming out of this, because he has had all the attention, be focused now on two issues.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "And, Ben Ferguson, is Senator Cruz hero or villain in all this?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Well, if you have a bigger gain plan is what happens next -- Ben Ferguson unless I'm misreading this, I would imagine come tomorrow and certainly all of next week what we'll see from Senator Ted Cruz is a rampaging of sort on Obama Care, right?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I think the only --", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "You think?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "Only people fainting at her at her rallies are going to be chubby gals from now.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Even Hillary Clinton?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "I kind of hope so.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "ORGAN: Do you think she will be the Democrat nominee?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Obama.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "Who would you next fear on the Democrat side?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Well, that remains to be seen.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "Who is the most electable right now?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "Your vote makes it very clear.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "If he were the Republican candidate?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "I'm not sure, I want to see them in debates.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "I'm saying who do you think can exercise your desire to have a winner?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "We'll see, it is very possible.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "But, my point is that do you think that he could be more electable to a wider cross section just to win the nomination and mind you, a Republicans?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "And Republicans don't do that?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "Because that is all -- because there is no chapter more than ten pages, a lot of it is greatest hits of mine from the last ten years.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 653}, {"answer": "It is fun.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "It is fun, right?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "Disagree with most of it, but I agree to some of it.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "I not only write them, I research it myself, which is why I don't have a T.V. or radio show.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "No -- Do you actually write them yourself?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "Do you like being so polarizing?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "Well, my big goal was getting on this show.", "docId": "131016pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "What do you hope to achieve with the book?", "qSentId": 698}]